Manage services

Usage: railway.exe service [SERVICE] [COMMAND]

Commands:
  list      List services in the current environment [aliases: ls]
  delete    Delete a service from an environment [aliases: remove, rm]
  link      Link a service to the current project
  source    Connect or disconnect a service source
  status    Show deployment status for services
  logs      View logs from a service
  redeploy  Redeploy the latest deployment of a service
  restart   Restart the latest deployment of a service
  scale     Scale a service across regions
  files     Manage files in a service filesystem [aliases: file]
  help      Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Arguments:
  [SERVICE]  The service ID/name to link (deprecated: use 'service link' instead)

Options:
  -h, --help     Print help
  -V, --version  Print version

Examples:

  railway service list --json
  railway service delete --service api --environment production --yes --json
  railway service link api
  railway service source connect --repo owner/repo --branch main --service api
  railway service source disconnect --service api
  railway service files list /app --json
  railway service files browse /app
  railway service files download /app/data.db ./data.db --json
  railway service files upload ./seed.db /app/seed.db --json
  railway service files delete /app/data.db --yes --json
  railway service files rename /app/data.db /app/data-old.db --json

Automation notes:
  Destructive non-interactive runs must pass exact selectors and --yes.
  Prefer service IDs from `railway service list --json` when names may collide.

